

# JERSON MORENO

WEB DEVELOPER



Urb. San Miguel, #51-05. Cumana, Venezuela. 6101



+584147858984



jersonmr@gmail.com

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**























# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Organization

Communication

Team Work

Creativity

# **PROFILE**

Degree in Computer Science with more than 4 years of experience in web development facing me with many projects in both backend and frontend roles.

I like always keeping facing up new challenges and I try in the way of learn new tools and techniques to better up like programmer. On the same way I have facility to integrate me with teams presencial or remotely if is necessary.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

2020 - 2021

#### **INTAIMF**

I worked entirely with the Laravel framwork in the develop of an API done from zero who was consumed with Vue.js and Nuxt framework.

# **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

2020 - 2020

JAPAN GOURMET PASS https://japangourmetpass.com

I worked entirely with the Laravel framwork in the develop of an API done from zero who was consumed with Vue.js and Nuxt framework.

## **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

2019 - 2019

CHARGY https://chargy.com/

I worked entirely with the Laravel framwork in the develop of an API who was consumed with Vue.js and one mobile app.

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

2018 - 2019

AGUAYO https://aguayo.co

I worked in many projects like interface designer using style guides done with CSS and Sass and trying to apply the best practices to bring the prototypes to the final design.

## FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

2016-2018

CESTICOM, C.A. https://cesticom.com

I kept working with tools such as HTML, CSS and JS using frameworks like Bootstrap and preprocessors like Sass, integrating all to the Larvel framework.

# **EDUCATION**

COMPUTER SCIENCE DEGREE

2004-2014

Universidad de Oriente

# **PROFILES**



